{
    "subject": "resource/Lompoc,_California",
    "predicate": "property/populationDensitySqMi",
    "object": "auto",
    "human_readable": "The population density of Lompoc, California per square mile is auto.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9492578506469727,
            "question": "What is the population density of Lompoc, California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8512265682220459,
            "question": "Is the population density of Lompoc, California, high or low?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8233431577682495,
            "question": "How many people live per square mile in Lompoc, California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8037547469139099,
            "question": "What factors might influence the population density of Lompoc, California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.726992666721344,
            "question": "How does the population density of Lompoc compare to other cities in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6411181688308716,
            "question": "Are there any trends in population density changes in Lompoc over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5759403705596924,
            "question": "What are the implications of a high population density in a city like Lompoc?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5326799750328064,
            "question": "How does the population density of Lompoc relate to its economic and social characteristics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44615688920021057,
            "question": "Where is Lompoc, California located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3360174298286438,
            "question": "What unit is used to measure population density?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The population density of Lompoc, California per square mile is auto.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3842_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Lompoc, California located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3842_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the population density of Lompoc relate to its economic and social characteristics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3842_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the implications of a high population density in a city like Lompoc?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3842_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3842_47.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe provided documents do not explicitly state that the population density of Lompoc, California is \"auto\". However, they do mention different numbers for the population density of Lompoc (3,659 people per square mile in one document and 3,678/3,687.02/3,805.50 people per square mile in others) which could be considered as contradictory or inconsistent with the value \"auto\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided does support that the population density of Lompoc, California, is given as 3,659 people per square mile in one document and 3,687.02 people per square mile in another, but there's no mention of an \"auto.\" value for the population density, so the query with this incorrect information cannot be considered correct according to the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"3678\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The population density of a location (in this case Lompoc, California) is not 'auto'. It must be a specific number derived from the total population divided by the area size in square miles. In the context provided, it is mentioned that the population density of Lompoc, California is 3,687 people per square mile.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}